So let's talk about other features of Amazon Bedrock.
And of course, if they start appearing
in the exam a lot more, I will do deep dives on them.
But we have Amazon Bedrock Studio.
This is a UI that you give to your team,
and that allows your team to use Amazon Bedrock more easily,
and also to create applications faster.
There's Watermark Detection, which is a feature
of Amazon Bedrock to send an image to it.
And the feature will tell you if this image was generated
with Amazon Titan or not.
So now for pricing on Amazon Bedrock,
so you have the on-demand mode.
And this is where you pay as you go.
There's no commitment.
And you're going to get charge for text models
based on every input and output token processed
for embedding's model, again, for every input token processed.
And for image models, you're going
to be charged for every image generated.
This works with the base models only
that are provided as part of Amazon Bedrock.
If you want to have some cost savings,
you can use the batch mode.
So in the batch mode, you can make multiple predictions
at a time, and the output is going to be a single file
in Amazon S3.
And by using batch mode, you're going to get responses
a bit later than in real time.
But at least you're going to get discounts of up to 50%.
For provision throughput, this is when you want to purchase
model units for a certain time,
for example, for one month or six month,
and you're going to get a guaranteed throughput.
That means that you're going to get
a maximum number of input and output tokens processed
per minute as a guaranteed.
And the idea is that you're going to maintain capacity
and performance, which is very important,
but it does not necessarily provide you with cost savings.
So provision throughput works with base models,
but is necessary if you have a fine tune model
or custom models or imported models.
In this case, you cannot use on demand.
You have to use provision throughput.
So you need to also understand the pricing
behind improving a model.
So if you use prompt engineering,
this is when you have techniques
and we'll see them in the next section,
or techniques to improve the prompt in the output of a model,
well, this requires no further model training.
So there is no additional computation or fine tuning.
So this is very, very cheap to do.
If you use rag retrieval augmented generation,
it uses an external knowledge base,
and because the financial model does not everything.
So it's less complex.
There is no financial model change.
You don't need to retrain your model or define tuning,
but there is a cost, of course,
because now you need to have a vector database
and you have a system that allows you to access
that vector database.
Then we have instruction-based fine tuning.
So this is when the financial model is fine tune
with specific instructions,
and that requires additional computation,
but this is really done to steer
how the model is going to answer
a few important questions,
to set the tone maybe for the model.
And finally, the main adaptation fine tuning
is very expensive,
because now you're going to adapt the model,
train on the domain specific data sets,
and then includes creating a lot of data,
and then retraining them all with all the data,
remember it's unlabeled, whereas instruction-based
was labeled, and this requires intensive computation,
and so therefore, this intuitively will cost more
than instruction-based fine tuning.
So how can you do cost savings on Amazon bedrock?
Well, if you use the on-demand pricing model,
it's going to be great for unpredictable workload,
and you have no long-term commitments.
If using the batch mode,
you get up to 50% discounts,
but of course, you need to wait a little bit
for your results.
For provision throughputs, usually it's not a cost-saving measure.
The goal of it is to really reserve capacity
from AWS and their providers,
and so therefore, you should not use this
as a cost savings strategy.
If you modify the temperature, the top K,
or the top P parameter, you modify how the model is working,
but this has no impact on the pricing,
and if you have the model size in mind,
usually a smaller model is going to be cheaper,
but again, this varies on who you get the model from.
So one of the main driver of cost savings in Amazon bedrock
is to modify the number of input and output tokens.
This is the main driver of cost,
so try to get you prompt as efficiently written as possible,
and try to get you output as concise and short as possible,
as well, if you are worried about cost savings.
So that's it for this lecture.
I hope you liked it,
and I will see you in the next lecture.